Is it okay if I bring someone to your parents' anniversary?
我可以帶人去參加 你爸媽的結婚週年派對嗎？
-Sure. -Yeah.
-沒問題 -好啊
-Who's the guy? -Parker, we met at the cleaners.
-你要帶誰去？ -派克，我們在洗衣店裡認識
Did he put a little starch in your bloomers?
他把漿糊放在你的外套裡？
Who said that?
是誰說的？
No, he's really great, though. He has this incredible zest for life.
不，但他真的很棒 他對生命非常狂熱
He treats me like a queen. Except when he treats me like a naughty girl.
他把我當女王一樣 但有時他當我是頑皮女孩
Would it be okay if I give the toast?
我可以致詞嗎？
Even after what happened at their 20th?
即使經過 他們20週年紀念日的意外後？
-I'd really like to. -Hopefully this time Mom won't boo you.
-我真的很想 -希望這次媽不會噓你
Yes! Every year Ross makes the toast, and it always makes them cry.
對，每年都是羅斯致詞 他把他們都弄哭了
-This year, I'm gonna make them cry. -You wonder why Ross is their favorite?
-今年我要把他們弄哭 -你知道他們為什麼最愛羅斯嗎？
Any time Ross makes a toast, everyone cries and pats him on the back.
只要羅斯一致詞 大家都會哭著拍他的背
And they all come up to me and say, "God, your brother."
他們都來跟我說 「天啊，你哥哥」
You know what they're gonna say this year? "God, you."
你知道他們今年會怎麼說嗎？ 「天啊，你」
Well, at least one person will be crying.
至少有個人會哭
I'm an actor, and any actor worth his salt can cry on cue.
我是演員 演員隨時都可以哭
-Really? You can do that? -Oh, you kidding me? Watch.
-真的嗎？你做的到嗎？ -你是在開玩笑嗎？看著
Well, I can't do it with you guys watching me!
你們盯著我看 我辦不到
The One In Massapequa
本集播出：馬沙皮卡市
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey.
嘿
Oh, my God. You look so fantastic.
天啊 你看起來美極了
On my way over, I pictured you in my mind's eye.
我在來這裡的路上 用我的心靈之眼想像你的模樣
Now I'm like, "Mind's eye, you had no idea!"
現在我想說 「心靈之眼，你錯了」
-Let's do that again! -Okay.
-我們再來一次 -好吧
-What are you doing? -I'm working on my toast.
-你在做什麼？ -我在寫我的演講稿
Or as I like to call it: "Sob-fest 2002."
或許我該叫它 「2002年最佳催淚彈」
I cannot wait to see them cry.
我等不及要看他們哭了
It's not gonna be like regular crying. It's gonna be like Terms of Endearment crying.
那不是一般的哭泣 他們會跟親密關係裡的演員一樣大哭
I'm gonna reduce my parents to sniffling, quaking masses of..
我要我爸媽痛哭流涕…
I may have some unresolved anger from my childhood.
我可能還在為小時候的事 生我爸媽的氣
-Hey, check this out. -It's a dog.
-你看 -是小狗
It's a dead dog.
那是只死狗
Chi-Chi. She died when I was in high school.
琪琪在我高中時死掉了
-You're talking about a dead pet? -It's good stuff, huh?
-你要談一隻死狗？ -那個主題不錯吧？
Joey? You got a present for my parents?
喬伊 你準備好要送我爸媽的禮物了嗎？
In honor of their 35th anniversary, I had a star named after them.
為了紀念他們結婚35週年 我用他們的名字幫星星取名
-That is so cool. -And I got Kama Sutra for the Elderly.
-那真的太酷了 -我還買了老年人的性愛寶典
You know, I think maybe the one present is enough.
我想或許一樣禮物就夠了
-Do you guys have any extra ribbon? -Sure.
-你們有多餘的緞帶嗎？ -當然有
What do you need? We got lace, satin, sateen, raffia, gingham, felt..
你要什麼？我們有蕾絲 緞子、棉布、亞麻、條紋布，你…
And I think my testicles may be in here too.
我想我的蛋蛋 應該也在這裡
Chi-Chi! Oh, I loved this dog.
琪琪，我愛這隻狗
Monica couldn't get braces because Chi-Chi needed knee surgery.
摩妮卡沒裝牙套 因為琪琪得動膝蓋手術
-What? -You're the 200-pounder who rode her!
-什麼？ -你是騎著他跑的兩百磅重大胖子
Hey! Everybody, this is Parker. Parker, this is..
大伙們，他是派克 派克，這是…
No, don't tell me. Let me guess: Joey, Monica, Ross, Rachel..
不，別告訴我，讓我猜 喬伊，摩妮卡，羅斯，瑞秋…
and I'm sorry, Phoebe didn't mention you.
對不起 菲比沒有提過你
Chandler, I'm kidding! Already you're my favorite.
錢德，我是在開玩笑 你已經是我的最愛了
-Tell me a little about yourselves. -Actually, we should get going.
-跟我談談你的事 -事實上我們該走了
Classic Ross!
典型的羅斯
Rachel, look how you glow! May I?
瑞秋，你好漂亮，我可以嗎？
I think you already are.
我想你已經不請自來了
Rachel, you have life growing inside you.
瑞秋 你體內孕育著一個小生命
Is there anything more miraculous.. A picture of a dog! Whose is this?
有什麼更神奇… 一張狗照片，這是誰的狗？
That's my old dog. He passed away years ago.
那是我以前養的狗 他在好幾年前過世了
Well, at least you were lucky to have him. Bow-wow, old friend. Bow-wow.
至少你很幸運能擁有他 賤狗，我的老朋友
You guys, we really should get going.
大伙們，我們真的該走了
There I go again, my catch phrase.
我又犯了多話的老毛病
-So where's the party? -It's in Massapequa.
-派對在哪裡舉行？ -在馬沙皮卡
Massapequa, it sounds magical. Is it steeped in Native American history?
馬沙皮卡，聽起來跟魔法一樣 它是美國原住民歷史上的名勝嗎？
Well, there is an Arby's in the shape of a tepee.
那裡有原住民帳篷形狀的 艾比餐廳
I've got my notes. You got the presents?
我拿了紙條，你拿了禮物嗎？
-I've got the car keys. -We're driving? Aces.
-我拿了車鑰匙 -我們要開車嗎？太棒了
-So he seems like a nice guy. -Yeah, I like him a lot.
-他似乎是個好人 -對，我很喜歡他
-You want to hang back and take a cab? -Okay, otherwise I'm not going.
-你想被丟下搭計程車嗎？ -好吧，除非我不想去
-Hey, Mom. -This is such a great party!
-嘿，媽 -這個派對真的很棒
Thirty-five years. Impressive. Do you have any pearls of wisdom?
35年，太棒了 你們有什麼至理名言嗎？
-Jack? -Why serve food on such a sharp stick?
-傑克 -為什麼食物上要插著牙籤？
It's a good question, Dad. It's a good question.
那是個好問題，爸爸 那是個好問題
-Congratulations, you two. -Thank you, we're so excited.
-恭喜你們 -謝謝，我們很興奮
And also, congratulations on your wedding.
還要恭喜 你們結婚了
-Can we talk to you for just a moment? -Yeah.
-我們能跟你們談一下嗎？ -好吧
It's just a little thing.
這只是件小事
While we think it's marvelous you're having this baby out of wedlock..
我們覺得你們未婚生子 真的很棒…
our friends are less open-minded.
但我們的朋友沒有那麼開放
-We told them you're married. -What?
-我們告訴他們你們結婚了 -什麼？
Thanks for going along with this.
謝謝你們願意配合
-We have to pretend that we're married? -I had to shave my ears.
-我們得假裝我們結婚了 -我為了今晚必須要掏耳朵
You can do this.
這你至少可以做的
-Can you believe that? -I know.
-你能相信嗎？ -我知道
If you do the ears, you may as well take a pass at the nose.
如果你要掏耳朵 最好順便挖一下鼻子
I don't want to have to lie about being married.
我不想騙人說我結婚了
I don't either. But it's their party, and it's one night.
我也不想，但這是他們的派對 而且只有一晚而已
We don't have to lie. We won't talk.
我們不必說謊 我們只要不說話
If it comes up, we'll smile, we'll nod along..
如果有人提起 我們只要微笑點頭…
-Ross? -Rachel?
-羅斯 -瑞秋
Hi, Aunt Lisa. Uncle Dan.
嗨，麗莎阿姨，丹姨丈
Congratulations on the baby and on the wedding.
恭喜你們懷孕 還結了婚
-Here's something to start you out. -How's marriage treating you?
-這是個好開始 -你們婚後還好吧？
-Unbelievable. It's great! -We love marriage.
-不可思議，太棒了 -我們喜歡結婚
We'll see you later.
待會見
-Hey! -Hi!
-嘿 -嗨
Can I just say, Monica, that your driving is exquisite.
摩妮卡 你的駕駛技術太棒了
Thanks. Like I said before, I pretty much just stayed in the lines..
謝謝，我之前說過 我只是沒有越線…
and tried not to hit anybody.
試著不要撞到人
What a beautiful place. What a great night.
好漂亮的地方 好棒的夜晚
I have to tell you, being here with all of you in Event Room C..
我得告訴你們 能跟你們一起在C宴會廳…
I feel so lucky. Think of the good times that happened here.
我覺得好幸運 想想這裡曾有過的美好時光
The birthdays, the proms, the mitzvahs, both bar and bat!
生日，畢業舞會 猶太教戒規，酒後的喧嘩
None will compare with tonight. I don't want to forget it.
它們都比不上今晚 我不想忘了它
It's like I want to take a mental picture of you all. Click.
我想在我心裡 幫你們拍張照，喀
I don't think the flash went off.
我想閃光燈沒亮
-I'm gonna find the men's room. -I'll go with you.
-我要去男洗手間 -我跟你一起去
Somewhere there is someone with a tranquilizer gun..
有人躲在某個地方 拿著麻醉槍…
and a huge butterfly net looking for that man.
跟大蝴蝶網 在找那個傢伙
I have to go too, but I don't want him complimenting my thing.
我也想上廁所 但我不想讓他誇獎我的小弟弟
Glad we weren't in the car. Did he let up?
還好我們沒在車上 他發作了嗎？
He called the Long lsland Expressway a "concrete miracle."
他叫長島高速公路 是「水泥奇跡」
This room. This night.
這個房間，今晚
That waiter! His shoes! I must take a mental picture!
服務生，他的鞋子 我得用心拍張照片
Sorry.
抱歉
Were you guys making fun of Parker?
你們在取笑派克嗎？
That depends, how much did you hear?
那得看你聽到了多少
He's a little enthusiastic. What's wrong with that?
他是有點狂熱 那有什麼不對？
-It's so much. -Well, so what? I like him.
-他太過火了 -那又怎麼樣？我喜歡他
Do I make fun of the people you date? Tag, Janice, Mona.
我會取笑你們的約會對象嗎？ 泰格，珍妮絲，蒙娜
No, because friends don't do that. Do you want my opinion?
不，因為朋友不會那麼做 你們想知道我的想法嗎？
Your collective dating record reads like a who's who of human crap!
你們的約會紀錄 加起來跟人渣史差不多
-I feel terrible. -I know.
-我覺得好難過 -我知道
What was wrong with Mona?
蒙娜有哪裡不好？
-Open it, open it, open it. -Yeah, baby!
-快打開 -好的，寶貝
So we never got to hear about your wedding.
我們不知道你們結婚了
-We were surprised we weren't invited. -No, it was a small wedding.
-我們很訝異我們沒有被邀請 -不，婚禮的規模很小
But it was beautiful. It was small, but kind of spectacular.
但它很美 它麻雀雖小五臟俱全
-Where did you have it? -On a cliff in Barbados, at sunset.
-你們在哪裡舉行婚禮？ -在巴巴多斯懸崖上的黃昏婚禮
And Stevie Wonder sang " lsn't She Lovely" as I walked down the aisle.
我走上紅毯時 史提夫汪達唱著《她真美》
-Stevie's a family friend. -Oh, my God. That's amazing.
-史提夫是我們家的朋友 -天啊，那真的是太棒了
-I'd love to see pictures. -Yeah, so would I.
-我想看照片 -對，我也是
You wouldn't think Annie Liebowitz would forget to put film in the camera.
你們不會相信 安妮萊波維茲忘了裝底片
Would you excuse us for a second?
對不起
-What are you doing? -What? This may be my only wedding.
-你在做什麼？ -什麼？那可能是我唯一一場婚禮
-And I want it to be amazing. -Okay.
-我希望它真的很棒 -好吧
-Maybe I rode in on a Harley. -Ross, it has to be realistic.
-或許我該騎著哈雷機車入場 -羅斯，我們得編得很像真的
Say, are you okay? You seem kind of quiet.
你好嗎？你似乎很安靜
-No, I'm fine. I'm great. I'm with you. -And I'm with you. What a great time!
-我沒事，我跟你在一起 -我跟你在一起，真的是太棒了
Look at this plate bouncy thing.
看看這個送盤器
What an inspired solution to man's plate-dispensing problems.
這是個天才發明 解決了端盤子的問題
Oysters! Let me feed you. That's not necessary.
-生蠔，讓我來餵你 -你不必那麼做
-Please? -I don't eat..
-拜託 -我不吃…
-I won't quit until you try one. -Okay, fine.
-你不吃的話我絕不罷休 -好吧
-Good. -What're they like? I've never had one.
-很好 -它們是什麼味道？我從來沒吃過
-Try one. -They look too weird.
-試試看 -它們看起來好奇怪
I know, I know.
我知道
Listen, your family is really starting to warm up to me.
聽著，你的家人 真的開始喜歡我
You just kissed the caterer.
你剛剛吻了外燴人員
-What are you doing? -Going over my toast.
-你在做什麼？ -準備我的演講
會讓他們好好的嚇一跳
I can't wait. They'll cry so hard, they'll be fighting for breath.
我等不及了，他們會痛哭流涕 他們會喘不過氣來
If you want to, I could just hold them down and you could just..
如果你要的話 我可以抓住他們，讓你…
And my veil was lace, made by blind Belgian nuns.
我戴著蕾絲婚紗 它是由比利時盲修女織的
-Blind? -Not at first, but it's intricate work.
-盲人？ -本來不是的，但這工作非常傷眼力
They said even though they lost their sight, it was worth it.
她們說雖然她們眼睛看不見了 但這還是很值得的
-I bet you looked beautiful. -Well, I don't know.
-我敢說你看起來很漂亮 -我不知道
But there were some people that said I looked like a floating angel.
但有些賓客說 我看起來像飛天天使
-How did you propose? -Oh, yeah, that's a great story.
-你怎麼求婚的？ -對，那是個很棒的故事
Well, actually, I took her to the planetarium.
事實上 我帶她去看太陽系模型展
That's where we had our first date.
我們在那裡第一次約會
I had the room filled with lilies, her favorite flower.
我在房裡 放滿了她最喜歡的百合花
-That is so sweet! -I want to hear the rest!
-那真的太棒了 -我還想聽
Then Fred Astaire singing, "The Way You Look Tonight" came on..
佛列德艾斯塔唱著 《你今晚的樣子》…
the lights came down, I got on one knee..
燈光熄了，我單腳跪下
and written across the dome, in the stars, were the words:
圓頂另一端 在群星間寫著
"Will you marry me?"
「你願意嫁給我嗎？」
And the ring was the size of my fist.
戒指有我的拳頭那麼大
Hey, Phoebe? Look..
菲比，聽著…
I want to apologize. Okay? We were being jerks.
我想抱歉，好嗎？ 我們太壞了
-Parker's nice, I'd like to know him. -You better do it now.
-派克人很好，我想多瞭解他 -你最好快去找他
-Why? -Because I'm gonna kill him.
-為什麼？ -因為我要殺了他
-What? -He's too excited about everything.
-什麼？ -他對所有事都太熱衷了
I'm all for living, but this is the Gellers' 35th anniversary.
我也很喜歡生命 但這是蓋勒夫婦結婚35週年派對
Let's call a spade a spade. This party stinks.
就算我們扯平了 這個派對爛透了
I'm having the worst time.
我真的覺得無聊到極點
There was a line for the buffet, and when I got to the plates..
大家排隊拿食物 我拿到盤子時…
I slipped on a giant booger.
踩到一大坨鼻涕滑倒
Are you sure it wasn't an oyster?
你確定那不是生蠔嗎？
It could've been. I didn't look at it.
有可能，我沒看
I wiped it on Chandler's coat and got the hell out.
我把它抹在錢德的外套上 拔腿就溜
I thought he was a great guy. I was so excited about him.
我還以為他是個好人 我對他真的很期待
Well, hey, you should be excited about him.
嘿，你應該對他充滿期待
There's nothing wrong with him.
他沒有什麼不好的
-You think? -Yeah, know what?
-真的嗎？ -對，你知道嗎？
-We were all just being too negative. -You're right.
-我們太悲觀了 -你說的對
He's just embracing life. We could all stand to be more like Parker.
他只是在擁抱生命 我們可以跟派克學習
You know what? I'm like him! I'm a positive person!
你知道嗎？我就跟他一樣 我是個樂觀的人
-Actually, you have an edge. -What's that?
-事實上你說的對 -那是什麼？
-Oh, it's Parker! -Look, the Bunny Hop!
-是派克 -看，兔子舞
-Oh, I love it! -You do?
-我喜歡 -是嗎？
Are you kidding? People acting like animals to music? Come on!
你在開玩笑嗎？ 跟著音樂學動物跳舞？來吧
Okay, it's time for the toast.
好吧，該致詞了
I know normally Ross gives the toast, but this year I'll do it.
我知道一向都是由羅斯來致詞 但今年由我來
No, it's gonna be great. Really.
不，它真的很棒
Okay.
好的
Mom, Dad, when I got married..
媽，爸，我結婚時…
the thing that made me sure I could do it was the example you two set.
我很確定 我要以你們為榜樣
For that, and other things, I want to thank you.
為了那一點及其他事 我要感謝你們
I know I probably don't say it enough..
我想或許我不常那麼說…
but I love you.
但我愛你們
When I look around, I'm saddened by the thought of those who could not be here.
我轉頭一看，悲傷地想起 沒辦法出席的人
Nana, my beloved grandmother, who would so want to be here.
我親愛的外婆 她真的很想來
But she can't..
但她來不了…
because she's dead.
因為她死了
As is our dog, Chi-Chi.
還有我們的狗琪琪
I mean, look how cute she is.. was.
你們看他多可愛…那是以前的事了
Do me a favor, pass this to my parents.
幫我一個忙 請把這個傳給我爸媽
Remember she's dead, okay? Her and Nana, gone.
記住他死了，好嗎？ 他跟外婆都死了
Wow!
哇
Does anybody remember when..
有誰記得…
Debra Winger had to say goodbye to her children in Terms of Endearment?
黛博拉威格在《親蜜關係》中 得跟她的孩子們說再見的樣子？
Didn't see that?
你們沒看過？
No movie fans?!
沒有人是影癡？
You want to hear something sad?
你們想聽些悲傷的事嗎？
I was watching a 60 Minutes piece on orphans in Romania..
我在《60分鐘》 看到羅馬尼亞孤兒院的報導…
who have been so neglected that they were incapable of love.
他們遭到拋棄 無法愛人
You people are made of stone!
你們都是鐵血心腸
Here's to Mom and Dad. Whatever!
敬爸媽，隨便啦
Thank you, Monica. That was interesting.
謝謝摩妮卡 那真的是太有趣了
-Wasn't it interesting, Jack? -Why don't I remember this dog?
-那真的很有趣吧？傑克 -為什麼我不記得這隻狗？
Ross? Why don't you give us your toast now?
羅斯，你為什麼不為我們致詞？
Oh, no, Mom. It's just Monica this year.
不，媽 今年輪到摩妮卡了
You're not saying anything? On our 35th wedding anniversary?
在我們30週年派對上 你不致詞嗎？
No, of course.
當然不是
Everybody? I just wanted to say..
大伙們，我只是想…
on behalf of my new bride, Rachel..
代表我的新娘瑞秋…
and myself, that if..
跟我自己說…
if in 35 years, we're half as happy as you guys are..
如果我們結婚35年後 有你們一半幸福…
we'll count ourselves the luckiest people in the world.
我們會覺得 自己是全世界最幸運的人
Oh, Ross.
羅斯
I just wish Nana were alive to hear Ross' toast.
希望外婆還活著 聽到羅斯的致詞
My God, what a fantastically well-lit hallway.
天啊 這個走廊的燈光真漂亮
Can I get you something to drink, like a water and Valium?
你需要喝點東西嗎？ 譬如水跟鎮靜劑
I must say, this apartment, it's.. there are no words.
我得說這間公寓 它…我不知道該怎麼形容
-Thank God. -It's a haven.
-謝天謝地 -它是個天堂
-A third-floor paradise, a modern Eden. -Yeah, I know, I know. Gotcha.
-位於三樓的天堂，現代伊甸園 -我知道，我瞭解
Listen, why don't we just sit and relax, just be with each other quietly.
聽著，我們為什麼不坐下來放輕鬆 安靜地彼此依偎
That sounds great.
聽起來很不錯
This is the most comfortable couch I've ever sat on.
這是我坐過 最舒服的沙發
Let's try something. Let's play a game.
我們試試別的點子 我們來玩遊戲
-I love games. -Shocking.
-我喜歡玩遊戲 -太棒了
Let's play the game of..
我們來玩…
who can stay quiet the longest.
誰能最久不說話的遊戲
Or Jenga.
或層層疊
Let's play this one first, and remember, whoever talks first loses.
我們先玩這個 記住，先說話的人就輸了
-I lose, now Jenga. -Oh, my God.
-我輸了，現在來玩層層疊 -我的天啊
-Is something wrong? -You know the word "wrong"?
-哪裡不對勁嗎？ -你知道什麼是「不對勁」嗎？
Everything isn't perfect or magical?
一切不是美好又神奇嗎？
Everything isn't aglow with the light of fairies?
一切不是都在 發光發亮嗎？
They were just brake lights, Parker!
那只是剎車燈，派克
Excuse me for putting a good spin on a traffic jam.
對不起，我美化了塞車
You don't have to put a good spin on everything!
你不必美化所有事
-I'm sorry. I'm a positive person. -No, I'm a positive person.
-抱歉，我是個樂觀的人 -不，我是個樂觀的人
You are like Santa Claus on Prozac.
你像吃抗憂鬱藥的耶誕老人
At Disneyland, getting laid!
在迪士尼樂園被上
You want me to be negative? You want me to be less happy?
你要我悲觀嗎？ 你要我不快樂嗎？
Much less happy.
非常不快樂
Fine. Well, then to quote Ross, "I better be going."
好吧，引用羅斯的話 「我最好走了」
So long!
再見
Don't let the "best door in the world" hit you in the ass on your way out.
別讓「全世界最棒的門」 在你出去時打到你的屁股了
Isn't this the most incredible fight you've had in your life?
這是你一輩子 吵過最不可思議的架吧？
We could've gone from the ceremony to the reception with you in the sidecar.
你坐在邊車裡 我們從婚禮現場走到接待處
It just isn't feasible.
那行不通
But a dove placing the ring on your finger would've been no problem.
但鴿子停在你的戒指上 就沒有問題
-It was fun being married to you. -Yeah, and it was an easy 400 bucks.
-跟你結婚真的太棒了 -對，這四百塊真好賺
-Okay, Ross, can I ask you something? -Yeah.
-羅斯，我能問你一件事嗎？ -好吧
-That proposal at the planetarium? -I know, I know. It was stupid.
-在天文館求婚？ -我知道，那太蠢了
Are you kidding? With the lilies, and the song and the stars?
你在開玩笑嗎？ 有百合花、歌跟星星？
It was really wonderful. Did you just make that up?
那真的是太棒了 你是隨便編的嗎？
I thought of it when we were going out.
我們交往時 我想過要那麼做
That's how I imagined I would ask you to marry me.
我想像過那樣子向你求婚
Wow.
哇
Well, that would've been very hard to say no to.
要拒絕你一定很難
It's a good thing I didn't do it, it sounds like a very expensive wedding.
還好我沒有那麼做 聽起來那會是個昂貴的婚禮
-Okay, good night. -Good night.
-好吧，晚安 -晚安
Even if the sidecar had a windscreen to protect your hair?
即使邊車有擋風玻璃 不弄亂你的頭髮？
-I will think about it. -That's all I'm asking.
-我會考慮的 -我已經滿足了
Okay, that's it. I give up.
好吧，夠了，我放棄了
At Mom and Dad's 40th anniversary, you give the speech.
在爸媽的40週年派對上 由你來致詞
You know, I don't understand why they didn't cry.
我不瞭解他們為什麼沒哭 你的致詞真感人
-Come on. -That stuff you said about true love?
-好了 -你說關於真愛的事？
You were right. We did learn a lot from Mom and Dad.
你說的對 我們從爸媽那裡學到了很多
That picture of Chi-Chi with her mischievous grin.
琪琪在照片上 調皮地笑著
And what you said about Nana? Yeah, she really would've wanted to be there.
還有外婆那一段 她真的會很想去參加
And you know what?
你知道嗎？
I think she was.
我想她去了
Oh, good God, Ross, how the hell do you do it?
天啊，羅斯 你是怎麼辦到的？